We need new voices.
Voices that can ask
the right questions.
[Host 1] How will
artificial intelligence change the world?
[Host 2]
The risks of artificial intelligence.
[Host 3]
Artificial intelligence.
[Host 4]
The big revolution.
[Host 5]
Supercomputers.
[Host 6]
Penetrating all fields.
Voices that help us understand
the changing world around us.
Day by day,
and minute by minute.
Voices that will
help us deal with
unprecedented
technological leaps.
Artificial intelligence...
Machine learning...
Large language models...
What do they mean?
And how do we
navigate our new world
responsibly and ethically?
Voices that can
make sense of all the data
and measure its
effects on our lives.
Voices that
can spot trends,
and point out
the gaps.
Voices that represent us
in conversations,
locally and globally.
A regional platform
for the Middle East
and North Africa.
Bringing together
policymakers,
researchers, civil society,
and people
who are passionate about
knowledge for everyone.
We need voices
that can respond to
the most important
question we face today:
What does the future look like?